the following content is provided under a Creative Commons license
以下内容是根据Creative Commons授权提供
your support will help MIT OpenCourseWare continue to offer
您的支持将有助于麻省理工学院开放式课程继续报价
high-quality educational resources for free
免费优质教育资源
to make a donation or view additional materials from hundreds of them IT
进行捐赠或查看附加材料由数百人资讯
courses
课程
visit MIT OpenCourseWare at 0 CW
参观麻省理工学院开放式课程在0 CW
that MIT that EDU ha for the
麻省理工学院的EDU公顷的
the
该
the in
在该
the new the we concluded the last lecture
我们得出的结论，最后讲座在新的
with the statement above the sampling theorem and just as a quick reminder
与上述采样定理，只是作为一个快速提醒的声明
the sampling theorem said that
采样定理说
if we have a continuous-time signal
如果我们有一个连续时间信号
and we have equally spaced samples
我们已经等距样本
all that signal sampled at a sampling period which a indicators capital T
在一个采样周期的一个指标大写字母T的所有信号采样
and if except he is banned limited
如果除了他是被禁止的限制
in other words the forty a transformer 0
换句话说，40的变压器0
outside some band where Omega Sapan
一些带以外的地方欧米茄萨班
is the highest frequency then
是最高的频率，然后
under the condition that the sampling frequency which is two-part divided by
采样频率是分为两个部分的情况下
the period
期间
is greater than twice the highest frequency
大于最高频率的两倍
the original signal is uniquely
原始信号是唯一
recoverable from the set of samples and
可收回的样本集与
the sampling theorem essentially was derived by
采样定理本质上推导出了
observing or using the notion that
观察或使用的概念，即
sampling could be done by multiplication
采样可以用乘法来完成
or modulation with an impulse train and the sampling theorem develop
或调制与脉冲串和采样定理发展
by examining the consequence
通过检查结果
love the modulation property in the context of the Fourier transform
爱的傅里叶变换的情况下的调制特性
in particular if we have our signal accept T
特别是如果我们有我们的信号接受Ŧ
and it's multiplied by an impulse train
而且它乘以一个脉冲串
to give us a sampled signal
给我们一个采样信号
another impose train whose values or areas are samples of the original time
另一处以串，其值或地区是原来的时间样本
function
功能
as i indicate here then
我在此说明，然后
in fact if we examine this equation or equivalently
事实上，如果我们研究这个方程或等价
bringing accept T inside this some
将接受Ŧ这里面的一些
if we examine either if these equations in the frequency domain
如果我们检查或者如果在频域中这些方程
the four EA transform love
四EA变换的爱
exe PFT is the convolution
exe文件PFT是卷积
above the 40 a transformer the original signal and the Fourier transform
40一个变压器的原信号和傅里叶变换上述
up the impulse train now
现在向上的冲动列车
be imposed strain is a periodic signal its Fourier transform
施加应变是周期信号的傅立叶变换
therefore as we talked about with Fourier transforms itself an impulse
因此，当我们谈到与傅里叶变换自己的冲动
train
火车
and when we do this convolution n
当我们这样做卷积Ñ
using the fact that the 48 race for the imposed strain
使用的事实，48族的施加应变
is an impulse train the result
是一个脉冲串的结果
or this convolution then tells us
或本卷积然后告诉我们
that the 48 transform love
该48变换的爱
the sampled signal or the impulse train
采样的信号或脉冲串
which represents the samples is a some
它代表了样品是一些
love frequency shifted replications
爱的频率偏移复制
up the 48 transform of the original signal
最多48个变换原信号的
so mathematically
所以数学
that's the relationship it essentially says that after sampling or modulation
这是它本质上说，关系是抽样或调制后
with an impulse train
用脉冲串
the resulting spectrum is the original spectrum
所得到的频谱是原来的频谱
added to itself shifted by multiples
添加到本身的倍数偏移
integer multiples of the sampling frequency well
的采样频率的整数倍以及
let's see that as we did last time in terms of pictures
让我们来看看，当我们在画面方面做了最后一次
and again to remind you of the basic
并再次提醒了基本的你
picture involved if we have an original signal
涉及的图片，如果我们有一个原始信号
with the spectrum is a indicated here where
与频谱是在此间表示，其中
its ban limited with the highest frequency Omega Savannah M
禁令限制最高频率欧米茄萨凡纳M
and if the time function is sample
如果时间函数是样本
so that in the frequency domain week involved this spectrum
以便在频域中周参与该频谱
with the spectrum shown below which is the
与图所示的频谱是
spectrum love the impulse train
谱爱的冲动列车
the convolution if these true up these two
卷积如果这些属实了这两个
is then the Fourier transform or spectrum
然后，在付里叶变换或频谱
love the sampled time function
爱的采样时间功能
and so thats what we end up with here
所以那是什么，我们结束了在这里
and then as you recall to recover the original time function
然后，你记得，以恢复原来的时间函数
from this as long as these individual triangles don't overlap
从此，只要这些个体三角形不重叠
to recover it just simply involves
恢复它只是简单地涉及
passing the impulse train through a low-pass filter in effect
通过脉冲列通过有效的低通滤波器
extracting just one of these replications
提取这些重复的只是一个
love the original spectrum
爱情原来频谱
so the overall system
所以在整个系统
then for for doing the sampling and then
然后做采样，然后
the reconstruction of the original signal from the samples
原始信号的从样品中的重建
consists of multiplying the original time function
由乘以原时间功能
by an impulse train and that gives us
由一个脉冲串并给我们
then the sampled signal
然后将采样信号
the Fourier transform I show here love the
傅立叶变换我在这里展示爱
original signal and after modulation with the impulse train
原始信号和调制的脉冲序列后
the resulting spectrum that we have is
由此产生的频谱，我们已经是
that replicated around integer multiples of the sampling frequency
周围的采样频率的整数倍复制
and then finally to recover
然后终于恢复
the original signal or to generate a reconstructed signal
原始信号或生成再生信号
we then multiply this in the frequency domain
我们再乘以在频域
by the frequency response of an idea low-pass filter
由一个想法的低通滤波器的频率响应
and what that accomplishes forest and
什么是完成森林和
is recovering the original signal
正在恢复的原始信号
now in this picture an important point that I raise last time
现在在这张图片中一个重要的一点，我提出最后一次
relates to the fact dead in doing the reconstruction
在这样做的重建涉及以下事实：死
well we've assumed is dead in replicating
以及我们已经假设是死在复制
these individual versions
这些个别版本
0 the original signal
0原始信号
those replications don't overlap and sold by passing this through a low-pass
那些重复不重叠并通过一个低通通过本售
filter in fact
事实上筛选
we can recover the original signal well
我们可以恢复原始信号以及
what that requires is that
什么，需要的是
this frequency Omega Savannah M be less than
这个频率欧米茄萨凡纳M是小于
this frequency and this frequency
这个频率和当前频率
is Omega so fast minus Omega serve them
欧米茄是如此之快减去欧米茄为他们服务
and so what we require is dead the frequency Omega Sapan
所以我们需要的是死者的频率欧米茄萨班
be less than Omega cyb s minus Omega sed am
小于欧米茄CYB零下欧米茄sed的正
or equivalent Lee what we require is that the sampling frequency
或等效李我们需要的是，采样频率
be greater and twice the highest frequency
更大和两倍的最高频率
in the original signal now
现在在原始信号
if in fact that condition is violated
如果事实上该条件被违反
then we end up with a very important effect
那么，我们结束了一个非常重要的作用
and that effect is referred to as a leasing
并且这种效果被称为一个租赁
in particular if we look back at are
特别是如果我们回头看是
original example we're here
原来例如我们在这里
we were able to recover our original spectrum by
我们能够通过恢复我们原有的频谱
low-pass filtering if in fact
低通滤波，如果实际上
the sampling frequency is
采样频率为
not high enough to avoid aliasing
没有高到足以避免混淆
then what happens in that case is that the individual replications
然后会发生什么在这种情况下是个人复制
love the Fourier transform above the stove the original signal
爱的傅里叶变换放在火炉上方原始信号
overlap and what we end up with
重叠，我们结束了
is some distortion as you can see if we tried to pass this through a low-pass
是有些失真，你可以看到，如果我们试图通过一个低通通过这
filter
过滤器
to recover the original signal in fact we won't recover the original signal
以恢复原始信号，事实上，我们将无法恢复原始信号
since these individual replications have overlapped
因为这些个别的重复发生交叠
and this is the case where Omega service minus Omega Savannah is less than
而这正是欧米茄服务减去欧米茄萨凡纳小于的情况下
Omega so vast in other words the sampling frequency is not greater
欧米茄换句话说，如此庞大的采样频率不大于
in this case than twice the highest frequency
在这种情况下，比最高频率的两倍
so what happens here then is that in effect
所以这里发生的事情则是，在效果
higher frequencies get folded down into lower frequencies what would come out of
更高的频率得到向下折叠成较低的频率有什么会出来的
the low-pass filter
低通滤波器
is the reflection of some higher frequencies into lower frequencies
是一些较高频率下的反射成较低频率
as I suggested a minute ago that affect
我建议在一分钟前，影响
is referred to as alias saying and in order to
被称为别名说，为了
both understand that term better and two understand in fact the effect better
双方都知道这个词好其实是两个认识的影响
it's useful to examine this a little more closely
要多一点仔细地检查这是非常有用
for the specific example a sinusoidal signal
对于特定的实施例的正弦信号
so let's concentrate on that and what we want to look at
所以让我们专注于这一点，我们想看看
is the effect or alias saying
该效果或别名说
when our input signal is a sinusoidal signal
当我们的输入信号是正弦信号
now to do that what I wanna show shortly
现在做什么我想不久秀
is a computer-generated movie
是一个计算机生成的电影
that we've made and let's first walk-through
我们所做的，让我们先步行通过
a few frames a bit to give you our first of all
几帧有点给你我们首先
to to set up our notation and to suggest what it is that we're trying to
要建立我们的符号，并提出它是什么，我们正在努力
demonstrate
演示
well what we have is an input signal
以及我们所拥有的是一个输入信号
is a sinusoidal signal and
是一个正弦信号，并
the spectrum or for a transformer that
频谱或变压器，其
is an impulse in the frequency domain at
是在频域中的脉冲在
the frequency the sinusoid we then
频率的正弦信号，我们再
have samples love that and when we sample that in for this particular
有样品爱，当我们品尝，在这个特殊的
example its sample the 10 killer hurts
例如它的样本的10杀手伤害
this spectrum is then replicated
这个频谱，然后复制
at multiples all the sampling frequency
在所有倍数采样频率
and I haven't shown negative frequencies here but the contribution do
我还没有在这里显示负频率，但做贡献
to the negative frequency
到负频率
is at 10 killer hurts minus the input sinusoid
是在10杀手伤害减去输入正弦
we then carry out a reconstruction
我们再进行重建
with an idea low-pass filter and the ideal ok pass filter is set at
一个想法的低通滤波器和理想确定通滤波器设置在
half the sampling frequency or five kelleher its
采样频率的一半或五凯莱赫其
so what we have then is
还等什么，我们则是
the input signal accept T
输入信号接受Ŧ
and the impulse train exe PFT
和脉冲串的exe PFT
and then the reconstructed signal is
然后将重构的信号是
the output from the low-pass filter
从低通滤波器的输出
which I denote as X a party
我记为X党
now as the input frequency X 50
现在随着输入频率×50
increases this impulse moves up in frequency
增加了这种冲动向上移动的频率
but this impulse moves down in frequency
但这种冲动的频率下移
and so let's just look at a few frames as the input frequency increases
所以就让我们看看几个帧作为输入频率的增加
so we have here a case
所以我们这里有一个案例
where the input frequency has move up
其中输入频率已经动起来
close to five killer hurts
接近5杀手伤害
as we continue further these two impossible's
当我们进一步继续这两个不可能的
will cross and what we'll end up with as i indicated
将交叉和我们将最终获得正如我
is aliasing so here now is a case
是走样所以现在这里的情况
where we have alias saying the
这里我们别名称
replication of the negative frequency has crossed into the passband if the
负频率的复制已经扩散到通带如果
filter
过滤器
and the reconstructed sinusoid will now
与重构正弦波现在将
be the frequency associated with this impulse
与这种冲动的频率有关
rather than the frequency Associated
而不是相关的频率
with the original sinusoid and to dramatize that
与原来的正弦波，并戏剧化了
even further here is
进一步这里是
the example where now the input frequency
这个例子现在所在的输入频率
has moved up close to 10 killer hurts
已经上升接近10杀手伤害
but what comes out of the low-pass filter
但出来的低通滤波器
is a much lower frequency and in fact
是一个低得多的频率，实际上
you can see that here is the reconstructed sinusoid
你可以看到，这里是重建的正弦曲线
whereas here we have the input size
而在这里，我们有输入大小
okay well now what I'm gonna wanna do is
还好现在好了我该怎么想要做的就是
demonstrate this as i indicated with a computer-generated movie
证明这一点正如我用计算机生成的电影
and well we'll see is the effect
而且还有我们将看到的是效果
on the effect of reconstructing
对重建的影响
from the samples using a low-pass filter
使用一个低通滤波器的采样
for an input which changes in frequency
对于一个输入而改变的频率
and with the sampling rate of 10 killer hurts
以及具有10杀手采样率疼
and what we'll see in the first part of this movie is
而我们会在这部电影的第一部分看到的是
the input except the and the reconstructed signal
输入以外的与重建的信号
X a party without explicitly showing the samples
没有明确显示的采样X派对
and then at a later point will also show this and indicate
然后在稍后的点也将显示这个和指示
that in fact the samples are those two are equal even though
这实际上将样品是那些两者相等，即使
they themselves are not
他们自己都没有
so at the top will have the input sinusoid without
所以在顶部将有输入正弦无
showing the samples and its
示出了示例和其
for EA transform is an impulse in the frequency domain as we've indicated
对EA变换是在频域中的脉冲，因为我们已经指出
and if we sample it that imposed and gets replicated
如果我们品尝它的征收，被复制
and so samples in particular
特别是这样的样品
will have a Fourier transform not only with an impulse
将有一个傅立叶与冲动，不仅变换
at the input sinusoid sinusoidal frequency but also attend killer hurts
在输入正弦正弦频率也顾不上疼杀手
minus that frequency
减去频率
now for the reconstruction we pass the samples through an idea low-pass filter
现在的重建，我们通过样本通过一个主意低通滤波器
I picked
我挑
the cutoff frequency of the low-pass filter at half the sampling frequency
低通滤波器的采样频率的一半的截止频率
namely 5 killer hurts
即5杀手伤害
and here we see is that the output
在这里，我们看到的是，输出
reconstructed signal in fact matches in frequency the input signal
事实上重构信号中频率的输入信号相匹配
now as we change the input frequency
现在我们改变输入频率
the reconstructed sinus so it is identical
重构的窦所以它是相同
until we get to an input frequency
直到我们得到一个输入频率
which exceeds half the sampling frequency
这超过采样频率的一半
at that point we have aliasing and while the input frequency is increasing
在这一点上我们已经走样，虽然输入频率的增加
the output frequency in fact is decreasing
事实上，输出频率降低
because that's what's inside the passband the filter
因为这是是在通带内的过滤器
now let's sweep it back and as the input frequency decreases the output frequency
现在让我们来扫回来和输入频率降低输出频率
increases
增加
till there's no aliasing and now the output reconstructed
直到有没有走样，现在重建的输出
signal is equal to the input
信号等于输入
so we sample the signal and then reconstructed
所以我们的采样信号，然后重建
the signal from the samples and keep in mind
从样品的信号和记住
that given a set of samples there are lots of continuous curves that we can
给定一个样本集有很多连续的曲线，我们可以
thread through the set of samples
通过该组样本的线程
the one that we picked up cores is the one consistent
我们拿起核心的一个是一个一致的
with the assumption about the signal band with
与有关与信号频带的假设
in particular we've reconstructed the signal
特别是，我们已经重建了信号
that who spectrum falls within the pass band at the filter
该谁光谱落在通频带内的过滤器
now what I'd like to show is the same
现在我想展示的是相同的
reconstruction and input as I showed before
重建和投入，我之前显示
but now let's look at the samples and what we'll see is that
但现在让我们来看看样品和我们将会看到的是，
when there's alias saying even though
当有别名的说法，即使
the output the reconstructed signal
输出的重构信号
is not identical to the input in fact
是不完全相同的输入实际上
it's consistent with the input samples that is sampling the reconstructed
它与输入采样是采样重构一致
signal
信号
gives a set of samples identical to the samples at the input
给出了一组样品的相同的输入样本
and it's just that the interpolation in between those samples
它只是在这些样品之间的插值
is an interpolation consistent with you soon
是插值与你很快一致
fan with love the input based on the sampling there
用爱风扇输入的基础上有采样
so let's now look at that with
让我们现在来看看与
the samples also shown along with the sinusoid
样品也伴随着正弦曲线所示
so at the top we have the input sinusoid together with its samples
所以在顶部，我们有输入正弦连同其样本
the bottom traces the Fourier transform of the sampled waveform
底部痕迹采样的波形的傅立叶变换
the middle trace is the reconstructed
中间的曲线是重建
sinusoid together with its samples and notice of course that the samples are
与它的样本，当然和通知，样品一起正弦
the input a reconstructed signal
输入一个重构信号
are identical and also
是相同的，也
the input sinusoidal frequency
输入正弦频率
and the output sinus or frequency are identical
和输出窦或频率是相同的
we now increase the frequency at the input
我们现在在输入频率增加
the reconstructed sinusoid tracks the input frequency
重建的正弦波与输入频率
and of course the samples are the two are identical
和当然的样品是两个完全相同
the interpolation in between the samples is identical
在样本之间的内插是相同
because the fact dead the input frequency is still
因为事实上死者的输入频率仍
less than half the sampling frequency
小于采样频率的一半
and so as long as the input is frequency is less than half the sampling frequency
因此，只要输入是频率小于采样频率的一半
not only will the samples be identical but also
不仅将样品是相同的，但也
the reconstructed continuous waveform will match
重建的连续波形匹配
the input way for
输入方式
now when we get to hear the sampling frequency were just
现在，当我们能听到的采样频率只是
on the verge Bailey is saying this isn't alias saying
濒临贝利是说这是不是说别名
quite yet but any increase in the input frequency
相当，但但在输入频率有所增加
will now generate aliasing we now have a leasing
现在会产生混淆，我们现在有一个租赁
the output frequency is lower than the input frequency but notice
输出频率比输入频率，但通知下
that the samples are identical now
该样品现已是相同的
the low-pass filter is interpolating in between those samples
低通滤波器是那些样本之间的内插中
with a sinusoid that falls within the past Pandev the low-pass filter
具有正弦曲线落在过去潘德夫内的低通滤波器
which no longer matches the frequency of the input sinusoid but
它不再匹配输入正弦波的频率，但
the important point is that even when we have alias saying
重要的一点是，即使我们有别名的说法
the samples are the reconstructed waveform
该样本是重建波形
are identical to the samples
是相同的样本
of the original way for and notice that as the input frequency increases
为原始的方式和通知，由于输入频率的增加
in fact the interpolated output the reconstructed output
事实上插值输出的再生输出
has decreased in frequency now as the input frequency begins to get closer to
减少频率现在随着输入频率开始变得更接近
10 killer hurts in fact you're all I
10杀手伤害，其实你是我的一切
tends to also interpolate between the samples
趋向于样品之间也插
with a frequency that is lower
用的频率是低
day and the input frequency NS particularly evident
天与输入频率纳秒特别明显
here notice that the input samples in fact
这里注意到，实际上输入样本
look like they would be associated
看起来他们将相关
with a much lower frequency sinusoid then in fact
以低得多的频率的正弦曲线，然后实际上
was the sinusoid the generated a lower frequency sinusoid
为正弦曲线的生成频率较低的正弦曲线
in fact corresponds to the reconstructed one now as we sit back down
其实相当于重建一个现在当我们坐在回落
the aliasing eventually disappears and the output sinus or tracks the input
混叠，最终消失，并且输出窦或跟踪输入
sinusoid in frequency
正弦波的频率
so we've seen the
因此，我们已经看到了
effective aliasing for sinusoidal signals and turns away forms
有效走样的正弦信号和转身离开的形式
now let's hear how it sounds now
现在让我们来听听它现在怎么听起来
what we have for this demonstration is
我们所拥有的这个演示是
an oscillator and
一个振荡器和
a sampler and the output of the sampler
一个取样器和采样器的输出
goes into a low-pass filter so the
进入一个低通滤波器，因此
input for from the oscillator goes into the sampler
输入用于从振荡器进入取样器
and the output the sampler
和输出端的取样
goes into the low-pass filter the
进入低通滤波器的
sampler frequency is 10 killer hurts
采样频率为10杀手伤害
and so the low-pass filter
和这样的低通滤波器
has a cutoff frequency as i indicate here
有一个截止频率，因为我在此说明
all five killer hurts and
所有五个杀手伤害和
what will listened to is the
什么会听取的是
reconstructed output as the
重构的输出作为
oscillator input frequency berries
振荡器输入频率浆果
and recall there what should happen is that
和召回有什么要发生的是，
when the oscillator input frequency gets past half the sampling frequency
当振荡器输入频率得到过去的采样频率的一半
we should hear aliasing so we'll start the oscillator it to kill her ex
我们应该听到走样所以我们将启动振荡器它杀死前夫
and keep in mind that what you see on the dial
并且记住，你在表盘上看到什么
is the input frequency which you here is the output frequency
是输入频率，你在这里是输出频率
as long as the input frequency is less than half the sampling frequency in
只要输入频率小于一半的采样频率
other words 5 killer hurts
换言之5杀手伤害
the reconstructed signal sounds identical to the input
重构的信号听起来与输入相同
now at five still hurts were right
现在五个还在疼是正确的
on the verge of aliasing and when we increase the input frequency past five
对混叠的边缘，当我们增加输入频率近五年
killer hurts
杀手伤害
the reconstructed frequency in fact will decrease
重建的频率实际上会降低
so as we move for example from 5 killer hurts
所以作为我们移动例如5杀手伤害
up to let's say 6 killer hurts
最多让我们说6伤凶手
sick still hurts in fact yes alias
生病还是会痛，其实是别名
down to what gets alias down to
下降到什么让别名下来
4 killer us so
4杀手我们这么
6 go over to the input is for killer hurts
6到对面的输入是杀手伤害
at the output now if we move up even further
在现在，如果我们移动了进一步的输出
7 kilohertz at the end pushed its alias down
7千赫在年底推它的别名下来
to three killer hurts at the outpost
三个凶手伤害的前哨
so bad dan is a audio demonstration and aliasing
如此糟糕丹是一种音频示范和走样
so to summarize
所以总结
if we sample signal and then reconstruct
如果我们采样信号，然后重构
from the samples using a low-pass filter as long as the sampling frequency is
使用一个低通滤波器，只要取样频率为样品
greater than twice the highest frequency in the signal
大于两倍的信号中的最高频率
we reconstruct exactly if on the other hand
我们确切地重建，如果在另一方面
the sampling frequency is too low less than twice the highest frequency
采样频率太低小于最高频率的两倍
then we get alias saying in other words
那么我们得到的别名说，换句话说
higher frequencies get folded or reflected
更高的频率得到折叠或反射
down into lower frequencies as they come through the low-pass filter
成较低的频率，因为它们都通过低通滤波器
now wanted the
现在想要的
common applications love the whole concept of sampling
常见的应用爱取样的整个概念
is the use sampling to convert a continuous-time signal into a
是利用采样转换成一个连续时间信号转换成
discrete-time signal to carry out
离散时间信号来进行
what's often referred to as discreet I processing
什么是通常被称为谨慎处理我
of continuous-time signals and this in fact is something that will be talking
连续时间信号，这其实是一些会说话
about
关于
in a fair amount of detail beginning with the next lecture
在细节与下一讲开始了相当数量的
but and let me indicate that for
但是，让我表明，对于
that kinda processing essentially what happens
这有点儿处理本质上发生了什么
is dead we begin with a continuous-time signal
死了，我们开始了连续时间信号
and convert it to a discrete-time signal
并将其转换为离散时间信号
carry out the discrete-time processing and then
进行离散时间处理，然后
convert back to continuous-time and
转换回连续时间和
the conversion from a continuous-time signal to a discrete-time
从连续时间信号以离散时间转换
signal in fact is done
事实上信号进行
by exploiting sampling specifically
通过利用专门的采样
by sampling the continuous-time signal
通过采样连续时间信号
with an impulse train and then
用脉冲串，然后
converting the impulse train into
转换脉冲串入
a sequence in a manner that all talk about in more detail
的方式，所有的更详细谈论的序列
next time now in doing that
现在在做下一次
of course as you can imagine it's important since we want
当然，你可以想像这一点很重要，因为我们希望
an accurate representation of the original continuous-time signal
原来的连续时间信号的准确表示
to choose the sampling frequency to very carefully avoid aliasing
选择采样频率非常小心地避免混淆
and so in fact in that context
所以其实在这方面
and in many other contexts alias saying is something
而且在许多其他情况下别名说法是什么
that we're very eager to avoid however
我们是非常渴望避免然而，
it's also important to understand that alias saying
但同样重要的是理解的别名说
isn't all bad and there are some very specific contexts in which
并不全是坏事，并有其中一些非常具体的语境
alias saying is very useful and very heavily exploited
别名的说法是非常有用的，非常沉重的剥削
one example love
一个例子爱
a very useful context valia saying is when
一个非常有用的上下文VALIA的说法是，当
you want to look at things that happen at frequencies
你想看看事情发生的频率
that you can't look at for one reason or another and sampling in a leasing is
你可以不看的一个原因或其他，并在租赁采样
used to map those into lower frequencies
用于映射到那些较低频率
one very common example of that is the use of the stroboscopic
中，一个很常见的例子是使用的频闪
which was invented by doctor how their chechen
它发明了医生的车臣如何
at MIT and sometime earlier in fact we had
在麻省理工学院和更早的某个时候，其实我们有
the opportunity to visit doctor Richard ins laboratory at MIT
有机会参观医生理查德INS实验室在麻省理工学院
and see some examples of this so I'd like to
和看一些这方面的例子，所以我想
at as a conclusion to this lecture take you
在作为一个结论，这个讲座带你
on visit to the stroke where and MIT
在访问行程的地方和麻省理工学院
in the lecture in discussing aliasing we've stressed
在讨论走样讲座，我们已经强调
the fact that in most situations it's something that would like to avoid
事实上，在大多数情况下，它的东西，想避免
however right now we're at MIT and stroll Valley
但是现在我们是在麻省理工学院和谷漫步
as it's called on the way to visit the laboratory
因为它叫途中参观实验室
Mike MIT colleague Professor are alleged
据称麦克麻省理工学院教授的同事
where in fact a leasing is an everyday occurrence
那里其实是一个租赁是家常便饭
basically the idea is to follow dead
基本思路是遵循死
it in fact you wanna make measurements
它其实是你想进行测量
at frequencies that for one reason or another
在频率的一个原因或其他
you can't measure their sampling and consequently aliasing
你无法衡量他们的取样，因此走样
can be used to bring those frequencies down into a frequency range that you can
可以用来将那些频率下降到一个频率范围，你可以
measure
测量
well professor edgerton alias
还有埃杰顿教​​授别名
da kitchen invented the strokes call
大厨房发明了招叫
for exactly that reason and kinda the idea is the fall
整整这个原因，有点想法是秋天
the I essentially is a low pass filter and so there are things that happen
在我本质上是一个低通滤波器，所以有事情发生
at frequencies boat which
在频率的船
your I contract and by
你的我的合同和
sampling with light poles sampling in time
随着时间灯杆取样抽检
what in effect you're able to do is sample in such a way
实际上你能够做什么样的是这样一种方式
that higher frequencies get alias
更高的频率得到别名
down to lower frequencies then factor I contract
下降到较低的频率，然后因子I合同
so let's take the look inside the where
因此，让我们的外观里面的地方
and in fact see no aspiration or
而事实上看没有诉求，或
the scroll and some its effects
滚动和一些其影响
will be here introduce you to my mighty colleague I kitchen
将在这里向你介绍我的同事浩浩荡荡我的厨房
in also by the way he this is a great place for kids of all ages
在也顺便说一下，他这是为所有年龄段的孩子的好地方
and so my daughter just insisted on coming along to
所以我的女儿刚执意跟着来
also helped out stock need you we could begin with you
还帮助缺货需要你，我们可以开始与你
just saying a little bit about what the strobe is in with some history is
只是说关于频闪是与历史上的一些东西一点点
steroids ring resemble an increase in a min ly
类固醇环类似于增加一个分LY
misses them losing on Lampson
想念他们失去蓝普
prices litter control rate planning on
价格产仔率控制在规划
school is not a good strategy is going to turn and we're going to look at.
学校不是一个好的策略是要转，我们要来看看。
motor striving on balance weight
电机努力平衡块
to set up some rhinos lesions in the spring
设置一些犀牛病变的春天
want to know more bring on the throne
想知道更多带来的宝座
by
you writer and
您作家和
throbs but just in the frequency the way
跳动，但只是在频率的方式
but corresponds to North influencer little more elusive
但对应于北影响者多一点难以捉摸
for the facts thought maybe we could the turn the stroller
对于认为事实也许我们可以在打开手推车
for a minute noon the but let me
一分钟，中午，但让我
point out the by the way there the fact that
指出了通过有方式的事实，即
when looking at this without the strong mind always say essentially
阅读本文时没有强烈的心灵总是说基本上
our frequencies that are I can attract so you can see the motor
我们的频率是多少能吸引所以你可以看到电机
turning and
车削和
we can really see other than then with the were we can see the movie the spring
我们真的能看到比当时其他的都可以看电影的春天
and so I get your point is that when we put the strobe on
所以我明白你的意思是，当我们把闸门上
who were essentially sampling this and no
谁是本质上取样本，并没有
you brought this stand with a frequency that there the
你的频率带来了这个立场，认为那里的
Riza with the track in fact
里扎与实际上的轨迹
the I guess if we turn the
我在想，如果我们把
incandescent light of loon
卢恩的白炽灯
the able to really bring out
将能真正带出
are the alias frequency so now we're what we're looking at in fact are the
是的别名频率所以现在我们我们正在寻找的东西实际上是
the earliest frequencies the street courses moving a lot faster than we see
最早的频率街道课程移动快了很多，比我们看到
it in their ranks
它在他们的行列
you know that's going on arena
你知道是怎么回事舞台
30 times second Bruins are
30第二次是熊
thirties and second occurs through the survivors include
三十年代，第二是通过幸存者包括
next move Rohingya figure 8a. saying you don't see that
未来移动罗兴亚图8a。说你看不到
yeah friend
是啊朋友
well we'll be seeing now is essentially second harmonic that
以及我们将现在看到的基本上是二次谐波的
someone okay
有人好吗
and just do you think you can make this spring dance around a little bit
，只是你认为你可以使周围一点点今年春天舞蹈
find taking this slow frequency soon as all around
发现服用这种缓慢的频率一声各地
okay it's really neat let's turn the lights back on
还好这真是整齐，让我们关灯回
weekend this is Charles president with anything 3 I'm
周末，这是总统查尔斯与任何3我
yeah has the third what's interesting now if we look at this and
是啊有第三有什么有趣的，如果现在我们来看看这个和
seeking a fifth just rolled off again
寻求第五刚刚推出再次起飞
earth okay noticed just think we look at the spring man although we can see is a
地球还好发现只是觉得我们来看看春天的人，虽然我们可以看到的是一个
blur
模糊
and really can't see because you're right here tracking
而且真的不能看，因为你在这里追踪
can see things happening station but he said
可以看到的事情发生站，但他说
by the way this was written demonstrated at the World's Fair
这个写的方式展示在世界博览会
the thickness
厚度
world because glasses
世界因为眼镜
for their Wow a loses all dressed up
他们哇失去所有打扮
element using
使用元素
break bring bruises
突破带来的瘀伤
fine but failed I stick with the miners stresses
不错，但失败了，我坚持与矿工讲
runners or have break
跑步者或有突破
bum they work on automobiles
流浪汉，他们对汽车的工作
their own thoughts on the vibrate but let's
自己的想法在震动，但让我们
earth buy levitra run this for a lot more than half an hour or a liberal
地球买艾力运行这个对于很多超过半小时或更宽松
name is continues
名字是继续
terms
条款
thing me maybe we can look at the
事情我也许我们可以看看
a couple other things have a about the fam
一对夫妇的其他事情有一个关于票价调整机制
brand the classic buzzed
品牌经典嗡嗡嗡
that's a good idea makes too much noise
这是一个好主意，使噪音太大
ok is to remove that over here that's just an ordinary like the fam
确定是要删除在这里，这只是一个普通的像FAM
has a mark on one plate surgeon
对一个板块外科医生的标志
identify you can get up to speed
找出你可以加快速度
know that this looks like a phantom was also demonstrated in the
知道这看起来像一个幽灵也证明在
world's fair few years ago yeah kinda been
世界博览会前几年是啊有点过
been does a movie
已经做了电影
quicken awake practicing in to and it was very fan
加快清醒执业中来，这是非常风扇
well one like it happened if the reform do
还有一个像它的发生，如果改革做
MGM and the Peters B Smith
米高梅和彼得斯乙史密斯
wanted he said he won miss royale up
希望他说他赢了皇家错过了
custard pie into it not don't know I'm a serious scientists for
蛋黄派进去又不是不知道我是一个严肃的科学家
sizes compromise on a I
尺寸妥协在我
so we dropped an egg into it in the news UCI's B-movie
所以我们在新闻UCI的B级电影降到一个鸡蛋进去
dropping 0 not known struggle there there was with the
下降0不知道有斗争有一个与
high-speed great remove yeah it's okay so
高速伟大删除是它没关系使
so again I guess without this true when we look at its
所以再次我想没有这个真实的，当我们来看看它的
what we're looking at our frequencies it are
我们正在寻找我们的频率是什么都
much higher than the I think following now with the stroke blindness
远远高于我觉得跟中风失明现在以下
you can see both the alias frequency and you can also see the original frequency
你可以看到这两个别名频率，你也可以看到原始频率
because we have the
因为我们有
investment line sweats I'm let's
投资行盗汗我让
turned down the the background lighting and
拒绝了背景照明和
stand then really all that were able to see or the aliasing
站在那么真的能看到所有或混淆
frequencies stand I guess
频率站在我猜
I guess when we see more than one market means that the
我想，当我们看到一个以上的市场意味着，
stay were actually running its and
逗留了实际运行的和
or guns is more and more things the the using
或枪是在使用的东西越来越多
lower radiation steroids because the plans aren't exactly the same
较低的辐射类固醇，因为计划是不完全一样
actually this gives me a chance illustrating other important correlated
实际上这给我说明的其他重要机会相关
to the lecture
在讲座
I'll that they could bring them to frequency
我会说，他们可以把他们的频率
so that re only get one more scorched
使再只得到一个更加焦灼
missus begins to move this is just one way there now
太太开始移动，这只是单向的，现在
okay so so the way we have now we've essentially alias the fan speed and so
好了，所以这样的方式，我们现在我们已经基本上别名风扇转速等
the
该
is just a little higher than the seeds and now
比更高的种子，现在只是一点点
on right at the sea and now if I could and just a little further in fact that
右边大海，现在如果我可以，只是稍微远一点的事实，
looks like the fans turning back hurts
貌似粉丝义无反顾疼
and if you think that this into context the leasing
如果你认为这为背景的租赁
its it's like this to impulses in the frequency domain
它是这样的冲动，以在频域
crossover in with you get an effective you and was mathematically
交叉与你得到一个有效的你，是数学
you get a phase reversed in
你得到扭转在相
no wasn't so I E I first understood have a leasing
没有没有那么威强刚开始理解有一个租赁
with Doc understood why stand with the western movies
与Doc明白了为什么站在与西方电影
a everyone's Ryan see the wagon wheels through November go backwards train and
一个人的Ryan看到货车车轮至十一月倒退培养和
there's there the
还有那里的
wagon wheels in western movie going backwards yes stressed
在西方电影货车车轮倒退是强调
and just see what you see is %um too much weaker on straight up so you get to
和刚才看到你所看到的是％庵太多弱上直线上升所以你能
just see greater frequency of so that's
刚刚看到的，这样的频率更高
you get to marched
你去游行
u-turn and Justin's governor and you think tourist
掉头和Justin的州长，你认为旅游
you impressed
你印象深刻
schoolroom its regular spirits
教室定期烈酒
all rights pictures in your honor older adults
在你的荣誉老年人所有权利图片
and I rising price revolution I guess another thing is that this demonstrates
而我的价格上涨革命我猜另一件事是，这表明
something that is
东西是
and I heard a long time ago which is its should never use a power so with the
我听说很久以前这是它永远不应该使用这样的电源与
fluorescent lights the is arrest like is a little bit of a stroke affecting
荧光灯的是逮捕状是影响中风的一点点
you could actually can misuse of that standing still make mistakes a
你可以真正可以滥用该地位的仍然犯错误一
strength that you think everything we are doing is a good friend of
你觉得一切我们正在做的实力是一个很好的朋友
no I don't think I want to try it out how are you this do you think that's
不，我不认为我想尝试一下，你怎么这样，你认为这是
any sores and wounds she knows it's going
任何溃疡和伤口，她知道这是怎么回事
sproule undergoing closest friends okay let's
斯普劳尔进行最亲密的朋友没关系，让我们
I'm actually we turn the lights back on again what's
我实际上我们把灯重新打开什么
their latest see once again is that we can see both the alias frequencies going
他们的最新再次看到的是，我们可以看到这两个别名频率会
to you that's
你这是
and we we can also see the higher frequencies because the
而我们，我们还可以看到更高的频率，因为
incandescent lighting its okay maybe we can be no
白炽灯它的好，也许我们不能
is parents take a look at some other
被父母看看其他一些
on things and when I guess I'm curious about is the distance you have over
对事，当我想我很好奇的是距离你有过
their kids
他们的孩子
doc maybe you can tell us what we have here
DOC也许你可以告诉我们什么，我们在这里
churros the this to show
油炸面包的这个展示
how you can get motion pictures on a Susan still pictures
你如何能得到电影的苏珊静态图片
the circle is repeated 12 times
圆圈重复12次
why does outer part over mmm on this site
为什么外部分在MMM本网站
in part on the other quiet place one time for a revolution on this
在另一方面安静的地方，一次为这个革命的一部分
you see the exactly as it is if I skip one picture each time
你看，正是因为它是，如果我跳过一个画面，每次
when you get there relative motions
当你到达那里的相对运动
mall the object is to show the ball rotating
商场的目的是要表明，球旋转
is this where that one depending on mood straw was going faster or slower
这其中，一个依赖于情绪稻草正想更快或更慢
and the other Uzan this way motion pictures went well
另Uzan这样电影顺利
100 years school long for photography drew pictures of people
百年学校长的摄影画人物照片
different animated features like the run yes great
不同的动画功能，如运行是很大的
is actually the title kinda busy aliasing can be fun conservatism
其实标题还挺忙别名可以很有趣保守主义
sterling if the speeds
英镑如果速度
or away if you get a lot of different things sorted veterans
或者路程，如果你得到了很多不同的东西整理老兵
go through ruin currently reaches speeds
经过废墟目前达到的速度
reserve a room in the rules it sounds
预订在它听起来规则
ok and the background blur basically the high frequencies the I can't follow
确定和背景虚化基本高频的，我不能跟随
and and then we're going to propose and then again we can see
和，然后我们要提出，然后再次，我们可以看到
frequencies it really is down the nets
频率果然是下网
rookie I ends right now I am one place for revolution sleep
我的菜鸟结束，现在我一个地方革命睡眠
see the corner the move is consuming records
见招消耗记录的角落
exactly the reasons there are an increasing frequency
正是理由有越来越频
of risk if 100 one server or early get the illusion that diamonds
风险，如果100一台服务器或提前得到的错觉，钻石
room in fact let's a let's really enhanced solution
房间其实是让我们一个让我们真正增强解决方案
Western the incandescent lights off
西方白炽灯的灯关
and now now are we seeing really you're the alias frequencies
现在现在，我们才看到你真正的别名频率
or or do you think this just adds
或者还是你觉得这只是增加了
looks like reading recognized through was doing rejoining licensing
看起来就像是经过重新加入做授权认可的读数
of is the same rules now lower watching is something also
的是同样的规则下现在观看的东西也
might point out of a for the
可能指向一个出来的
I'm the lecture for the course is that actually there
我在讲座的过程中是实际存在
there really are two sampling frequencies receiving one is this road
真的有接收一个两种取样频率是这条道路
and
和
which is the stroke that you're running the other is the inherent
这是，你正在运行的其他的行程的内在
Creamery for the TV that's running at 30 frames a second
克里默里该公司在30帧运行的第二个电视
and that's won the reasons by the way in dead people watching this
而这赢得了理由的方式死去的人看这个
on the video worst are in fact seeing
在最糟糕的视频，其实是看
Flickr or a feeding or modulation between
Flickr或之间的馈电或调制
the two on synchronize frame rates runner grievances
两对同步的帧速率委屈亚军
grow up so we get to of to a room credits
长大了，所以我们得到的一个房间学分
of to
对
roaming two runs on each other of
漫游在彼此的两个运行
of
you know it senator Reid's learning this
你知道它的参议员里德的这个学习
soon living room when all your friends
很快客厅时，你所有的朋友
I think would be a good terrific homered problem getting video Kors
我觉得这是一个很好的了不起的本垒打问题，让视频Kors的
they have them all sit down and analyze all the frequencies that they're seeing
他们有他们都坐下，并分析了所有他们所看到的频率
and what they're being alias through the evening event
而且他们通过晚上的事件是什么别名
it's a good view run the teacher I love you
这是一个很好视图下执行我爱你老师
who is great yeah remember these dudes list
谁是伟大的耶记住这些帅哥列表
I think that a chase a few people away from the courses good
我认为，一个追几个人远离课程好
cracks and you get you get involved in these offerings
裂缝，你会得到你涉足这些产品
rule ruler and what you can do for a KMS roots
排除尺子和你能为一个KMS根吗
let's bring you the incandescent lights back again
让我们给您带来的白炽灯回来了
just to remind everybody that in back row this or
只是提醒大家，在后排这个或
some some frequencies that are a lot higher than the ones that
有的一些频率是比那些高了很多了
we begin to get the impression that we're watching just the
我们开始得到我们看刚才的印象
motor running Frances Bean pattern on
电机运行弗朗西丝豆模式
long Dhaka have to
长达卡有
I have to say that there are many people I know they have as much fun in the work
我不得不说，有很多人，我知道他们有尽可能多的乐趣在工作
as you do
当你做
home like a man arm quote would but I'd like to
家就像一个人的手臂报价会，但我想
do now baby is take a look at one last experiment sure did
现在要做的宝宝来看看最后一个实验中确实这样做了
and what I'd like to do is a.m. is go take a look at the
和我想要做的是通告去看看的
I guess what sometimes is called the home
我猜有时也被称为家庭
well not the water graphics for men with thin air the minute dole pillar
还有没有水的图形，男性与空气稀薄分钟施舍支柱
hydraulic everything that's the 1i was thinking and let's take a look over
液压一切是那样的1I的想法，让我们一起来看看在
there
那里
okay one just in this Go internal war so
好一个只在这个转至内部战争等等
your doc this is the what did you got DP
您的文档，这是你得到了什么，DP
HHM bird double peddler hydraulic
HHM鸟双液压行商
happening machine Gary okay then it's a.m. so please
发生机加里·还好那么它的上午，所以请
it looks like continues dream up it is not its
它看起来像继续梦想了它是不是它的
pump over there something sixty post second so those owners
泵那边的东西60秒后如此的业主
coming out in spurts %uh so actually again it's
即将在苗头％呃所以实际上这又是
it's the the sixty boss is the second year I can follow
它是六十老板是第二年我可以按照
your eyes so is exactly basically looks like a blur
你的眼睛那么究竟是基本上看起来像一个模糊
ruseler it is a blur writers you learn output stroll on
ruseler它是一个模糊的作家你学习上漫步输出
okay grace start so again
还好恩典所以重新开始
I guess we have this a essentially alias then in
我想我们有这样一个基本的别名，然后在
and again with the incandescent light you can see both sky high frequency
并再次与白炽灯可以同时看到天空中高频
and the alias frequency its and
和别名频率和其
but see I guess that's with the frequency close to the sea and we can
但看到我想这是与频率接近大海，我们可以
adjusted so that is stop stop bothering me going to go out and then we can
调整，所以这是罢罢烦我要出去，然后我们就可以
actually make it go up
真正让他走了
scored anybody who is this South
打进任何人谁是这个南
yeah effect movie have just just again due to stress this point to the
耶效果的电影刚刚只是由于再次强调这一点的
class the the kind of the idea here the face reversal of course
类中的那种想法在这里当然面对逆转
you can see it in the time domain Chynoweth you just think about when the
你可以看到它在时域查诺韦思你只是想想，当
flashes of light
光的闪烁
come but if you think I love kind of these
来了，但如果你觉得我爱那种这些
impulses that we have in the frequency domain
我们已经在频域中的脉冲
and we're aliasing as we change the sampling frequency what happens is that
我们正在走样，因为我们改变采样频率是发生什么事了
these impulses crossover
这些冲动交叉
and what that means is that we get a phase reversal the pending
而这是什么意思是，我们得到了一个倒相悬而未解
on which faces are associated with
其上面是相关联
which side up the sea so that's kind of the idea the phase reversal
哪边的海所以这是一种观念的相位反转
okay let's the let's turn the
好吧，让我们的，让我们把
against because it is important thing in between those who got
反对，因为它是重要的事情在那些谁得到的
yeah let's let's turn the incandescent light of first and
是啊，让我们让我们先看的白炽灯和
think one thing your so 103 know through this thing you think you can do to get
想一件事你这样103知道通过这件事情你觉得你能做得到
on the other side you're on hand so we can see with
在另一边你在手，我们可以看到
when for the UN intervening sleuths
当对联合国干预侦探
water there all the time well on a nosedive it seems to me if we can't we
水那里所有的时间和状况急转直下，在我看来，如果我们不能我们
just the justices
只是法官
the that's just go through to next year staff the dots can do it just seeing how
在这只是经过明年工作人员的点可以这样做只是看如何
come you think your finger in the air
来到你认为你的手指在空中
fun to try once more its
有趣的尝试一次其
I get snyder et that's one thing we can do this
我得到Snyder等了一件事我们可以做到这一点
well as bring the lights back up and its
以及把灯背起来，其
again just to go stress the point scary RTC
只是再次去强调的一点吓人的RTC
there we are at a frequency that it's just a little above the sea
那里我们正处在一个频率，它只是一个小海拔
and we can go back there and in the sea and we can actually get a phase reversal
我们可以回到那里，并在海中，我们实际上可以得到一个相位反转
and I guess if we do this long enough we get at the at the whole ocean and put it
我想，如果我们做到这一点足够长的时间，我们得到的在整个海洋，并把它
back in
早在
we're ever comes from is there in cars in newsrooms gonna run is not running
我们永远来自是有汽车在编辑部要去跑不跑
too long by the Rev trailer get here yet to be careful as well as the Moody Blues
过长的牧师拖车来到这里还没有要小心，以及穆迪布鲁斯
V
surface well I don't know about them but I guess I believe you back its
表面好，我不知道他们，但我猜我相信你回来了
up a little more pressure on three gods monarchy
上三神君主多了几分压力
Adams girlfriends or service teams
亚当斯的女友或服务团队
going things together Ste
将东西放在一起科技教育
we have these machines are all over the place lot of fun
我们这些机器是所有的地方很多乐趣
but that this this is really terrific I i think that
但是，这是很了不起的我我认为
the this whole idea of the
的在这整个想法
and abusing aliens saying in stroz and
和滥用外星人说的stroz和
the kinds of things that did you do with the murder just fantastic in that we
这样的东西你做的谋杀真是太棒了，因为我们认为
really appreciate the chance to
真的很感谢有机会
come in here and see the demonstration Rose Bowl game ruth's
来这里，看到了示范​​玫瑰碗比赛露丝的
hope you will use it for years the bar over many years to come
希望你会使用它多年了吧多年来来
so is I emphasized that the beginning
那么，我强调的是，一开始
in what situations aliasing can in fact be very useful
在什么情况下走样，其实是非常有用的
also with this demonstrates is that particularly when you have a colleague
也与这表明的是，尤其是当你有一个同事
like da kitchen
像大厨房
a leasing and for that matter science in general can be an awful lot of fun
一般一个租赁及与此有关的科学可以是一个可怕的很多乐趣
by gonna thanks a lot that again and thank you just the name
通过会非常感谢一遍，感谢你刚才的名字
well I have to say that that visit was an awful lot of fun for me and
好，我不得不说，这次访问​​是非常多的乐趣，我和
for Justin in fact to for the whole camera crew that was
贾斯汀事实上，为整个摄制组，这是
there and hopefully you all have used at some point will also have a chance to
还有，希望大家都用在某些时候还会有机会
visited stroll Valley well
漫步参观以及谷
hopefully what we've gone through today gives you
希望我们已经通过了今天给你
a good feeling for the concepts love sampling an alias saying
一个很好的感觉的概念采样爱的别名说
and both why it might be useful and why we might want to avoid
无一不为什么它可能是有用的，我们为什么要避免
in the next lecture will continue on
在下一讲将继续
the discussion of sampling any particular
取样任何特定的讨论
what all be talking about is the interpretation
什么都可以说的是解释
love the reconstruction process not in the frequency domain
爱在频域重建过程中不
but in a time-domain interpretation specifically associated
但在时域的解释特别相关
with the concept %uh interpolating between the samples
这个概念％呃样本之间的插值
well then proceed from there too a discussion as i've alluded to
好然后再从那里过一个讨论，因为我已经提到
in several lectures love what i've referred to as
在几次讲座爱我所称为
discrete-time processing of continuous-time signals
连续时间信号的离散时间处理
very heavily exploiting the concept and issues associated with sample
非常严重剥削与样品相关的概念和问题
thank you
谢谢